{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209458754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209458754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209461908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209461907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209463459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209463459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJA"," userResponse":" KUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209466569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209466569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209468138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209468138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209471200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209471200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209472769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209472769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kufa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFA"," userResponse":" KUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209475829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209475828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kufa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209477398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209477398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209480637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209480637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209482199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209482199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuoa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOA"," userResponse":" KUOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209485495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209485495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuoa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209487071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209487071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209490065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209490065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209491633","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209491633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209493720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209493720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209495290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209495290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" KUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209498142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209498142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209499715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209499715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTA"," userResponse":" KUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209502694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209502694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ku.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209504707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209504706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549209504863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549209504863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_185722"," gameId":" b1055e8b-999e-4439-8f9a-c913753bfc45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ku.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}